[Waco] Clifton Manufacturing Company records, Inclusive: 1909-1987, undated, Bulk: 1946-1971, undated
Baylor University Libraries
- Product Information, 1910-1971, undated; 4
  - Standard Costs [Pants], 1971 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Photographs and Printing Plates, 1914-1987, undated; 5
  The Photographs and Printing Plates series, dated 1914-1987, includes general photographs from company events and products, advertisement cut sheets and original artwork, and copy for catalogs. Some photographs have been altered in preparation for use in printing plates. Plates are present in both metal and paper formats. A portion of the photographs are listed as undated, however, markings on the backs suggest they were created by the Windy Drum Studio which was active in Waco during the 1950s and 1960s. The series is in chronological order and in good condition.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Photo negative; Photographic print
  - Photographs: Air Conditioner Covers (1 of 2), undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Air Conditioner Covers (2 of 2), undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Buildings, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Photographs: Company Picnics, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Photographs: Factory Groups, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Photographs: General, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Groups, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Lawn Mower Covers, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: Residences, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: Roberts Clothes Outlet Display, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: Santone Building, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Seat Cover, General (Negatives), undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Seat Cushions, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Silla-Rey Dungarees, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Photographs: Tarpaulin on Luggage Rack, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Photographs: Tarpaulins, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Photographs: Tents (1 of 2), undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: Tents (2 of 2), undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Photographs: Warehouse Store, undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, Adjusta Cushions, undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Plates: Air Conditioner Covers, undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Plates: Airy Comfa Seats, undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Plates: Apronettes, undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Plates: Auto Cabanas, undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Plates: Clear Plastic Covers and Seat Covers, undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Plates: Cushions, undated (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Plates: General, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Plates: Motor Boat Covers, undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Plates: Seat Covers, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Plates: Ski Belts and Float Ropes, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Plates: Soak-N-Wet, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Plates: Terry Cloth [Seat] Covers, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Company Picnic, 1914-1955 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Factory Work, 1943-circa 1944 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Photographs: Meetings and Appearances, 1948-1970 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Photographs: Company Picnic, Group Photo, 1949-1951 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Photographs: Factory Work, circa 1950 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: Company Christmas Party, circa 1951 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Plates: Seat Covers, Jiffy Jeans, circa 1956 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Photographs: Auto Cabanas (Picnic Shelters) Styles #7 and #11, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Plates: Dust Cloths, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Photographs: Winter Liners, circa 1957 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Photographs: Auto Cabana Artwork, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: Gun Case Covers, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Photographs: Reel Covers, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: Seat Covers, General (1 of 2), 1957 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: Seat Covers, General (2 of 2), 1957 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Ski Belts, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Biltric Dome Pick-Up Tarps, Stake Body, 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Airy Comfa-Seat Pad, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Photographs: Outboard Motor Cover, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Artwork: News Ads, Seat Covers, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Artwork: Seat Covers, Kwikovers Advertisements, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Artwork: Ski Belts, undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Plates: Seat Covers, General, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Photographs: T.V. and Comfort Cushions, 1958-1959 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Photographs: Apronettes [Includes Artwork] (1 of 2), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Photographs: Apronettes [Includes Artwork] (2 of 2), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Photographs: Proofs of Cuts Used in 1959 Auto Catalog (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Photographs: Comfort Cushions, Supplement Sheet cc-359, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Cuts and Mats: Riviera and Lum Puf, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Photographs: General, 1959 June (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Seat Covers and Auto Cushions [Pillows], 1959 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: Seat Covers, Kwikovers Installation, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Seat Covers, Riviera, Satellite, Parklane, Superior, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Plates: Outboard Motor Covers, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Seat Covers, Catalogs 61, 634 & 900, circa 1961 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Photographs: Game Bag, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Plates: Seat Covers, Outlass Mats and Guarantee, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Plates: Seat Covers, Diplomat, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Photographs: Seat Covers Catalog #634 (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Photographs: Seat Covers Catalog #634 (2 of 2), 1963 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Plates: Seat Covers Cuts and Mats, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Photographs: Tractor Cushions and Seats, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Photographs: Personal, 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Plates: Seat Covers, 1965-1966 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Photographs: Buildings and Equipment, 1966-1981 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Photographs: Quality Award for Performance, 1967 June 29 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Photographs: Company Events, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Photographs: Albert L. Clifton, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 21)